我觉得爸爸想让我们继承他的事业
I think Dad wants us to pick up those he's left off.
帮助他人 猎杀恶灵
Saving people, hunting things.
这是家族事业
The family business.
（走过的路）
在炼狱中有着比那些灵魂更加古老的东西
There are things much older than souls in purgatory.
利维坦
Leviathan!
迪克要来了
Dick is coming.
如果你要赢
If you want to win,
你就得是佼佼者
then you got to be the shark.
而大鱼吃小鱼
A shark's got to eat.
鲍比
Bobby!
等你们的时候到了
When it's your time…
别留恋人世
go.
你到底是什么
What the hell are you?
他是上帝的先知
He's a prophet of the lord.
那就是神之语了
And that's the word of god?
没错
Yes.
上面写着关于利维坦的事
It's about Leviathan.
有写怎么杀死他们吗
Does it say anything about how to kill them?
我们这些魔怪死了之后 魂归何处呢
When we freaks die, where do we go?
就像你最糟的恶魔最阴暗的部分
It's like the backside of your worst nightmares.
充满了血腥尸骨和无尽的黑暗
It's all blood and bone and darkness.
炼狱
Purgatory.
斩其首 躯体挣扎凌乱
Cut off the head, and the body will flounder.
先知我带走了
Prophet's mine.
看来你这次真的是得独自面对了
You are well and truly on your own.
我们在炼狱
We're in purgatory?
小卡 我想我们还是
Cass, I think we better g…
小卡
Cass?
（如今）
（缅因州 一百英里原野）
（一年后）
威尔 快起来
Will, get up.
刚刚有什么事发生了
Something just happened.
去啊 别愣着
Go. Go do something.
我应该干什么…
W-what am I supposed to…
有人吗
Hello?
是只鹿
It was a deer.
我不清楚 像是一只鹿之类的
I don't know. It was like … it was a deer or some… oh!
这是哪儿
Where am I?
什么
What?
公路在哪里
Where's the road?
这边走下去12英里
12 miles that way.
（路易斯安那州 克莱顿）
（四天后）
（拉斐特）
这最好是你的坟 狗娘养的
This better be you, you son of a bitch.
等一等 你个混蛋
Hold on, you bastard.
别急
Hold on!
[咒语]
你动作倒挺快的
Wow. That was fast.
不能指望你啊
No thanks to you.
怎么耽搁了那么久
The hell took you so long?
不客气
You're welcome.
身体还好用吗
Everything working?
挺好了
Good enough.
那…
So…
现在怎么办
What now?
就按之前商定的来
Like we talked about, I guess.
那就此别过了
Then this is goodbye.
别惹事 本尼 听着了吗
Keep your nose clean, Benny. You hear me?
我们成功了 兄弟 我真不敢相信
We made it, brother. I can't believe it.
我俩都逃出来了
You and me both.
[邪恶力量 第8季第1集]
（得克萨斯州 克米特）
（蒙大拿州 恢特菲什）
迪恩 搞什么
Dean?! What the …
我不是恶魔
I'm not a demon.
也不是利维坦 搞什么
Or a Leviathan. What …
也不是易形者
Or a shifter.
很好
Good.
轮到我了
My turn.
来吧 开始
Come on. Let's go.
我才不要 我知道是你
I don't need to. I know it's you.
该死 萨姆
Damn it, Sammy!
来啊
Come on!
不 迪恩 我能就道声好吗
No! Dean, can I just say hello?
好了
All right.
现在来吧
Let's do this.
我都不知道是该跟你拥抱还是去洗个澡
I don't know whether to give you a hug or take a shower.
来吧
Come here.
哥们
Dude…
你居然还活着
You're…freakin' alive.
我是说 到底发生了什么
I mean, what the hell happened?
我猜是我们站得离迪克太近了
Well, I guess standing too close to exploding Dick.
爆炸把我们也送去了炼狱
sends your ass straight to purgatory.
你之前在炼狱里
You were in purgatory?
过了整整一年
For the whole year?
是啊 整天逃命的话时间就过得很快
Yeah, time flies when you're running for your life.
你怎么逃出来的
Well, how'd you get out?
我想建造了炼狱的人
I guess whoever built that box.
也并不想让我待在那儿
didn't want me in there any more than I did.
什么意思
What does that mean?
我出来了 就这样
I'm here, okay?
那小卡呢 他也在那里吗
What about Cass? Was he there?
小卡没能逃出来
Yeah, Cass didn't make it.
这到底是什么意思
What exactly does that mean?
他在下面出了点事
Something happened to him down there.
最后情况变得很糟糕
Things got pretty hairy towards the end,
于是他就放弃了
And he…just let go.
那小卡死了 你亲眼看见了吗
So Cass is dead? You saw him die?
我看得够多了
I saw enough.
那怎么说 你也不确定
So, then what, you're not sure?
我说了我看得够多了 萨姆
I said I saw enough, Sam.
好吧
Right.
迪恩 我很难过
Dean, I'm sorry.
我也是
Me too.
说说你 我都不敢相信你来了
So you … I can't believe you're actually here.
你知道你一半的号码都停机了吗
You know that half your numbers are out of service?
感觉给你的留言都打水漂了
Felt like I was leaving messages in the wind.
没错 我没收到你的留言
Yeah, I-I-I didn't get your messages.
怎么会的
How come?
大概是因为我把电话扔掉了
Probably because I ditched the phones.
原因呢
Because…?
我想…
I guess, um…
这一年里我也经历了很多事情
I guess something happened to me this year, too.
我不做猎人了
I don't hunt anymore.
是啊
Yeah.
萨莎·格蕾（美国著名AV女星）还去演正剧了呢
And Sasha Grey's gone legit.
怎么了
What?
没什么
Nothing.
她的确参演了一部索德伯格的电影
Um, she did a Soderbergh movie.
- 什么 - 她拍了部索德伯格的电影
- What? - She did a soderbergh.
不 说的是你 萨姆
No. You, Sam.
你退出了
You quit?
是的 因为你不见了 迪恩
Yeah. Yeah, I … you were gone…Dean.
小卡也不见了 鲍比也死了
Cass was gone, Bobby was dead.
克劳力把凯文和梅格不知道弄去了哪里
I mean, Crowley even shipped off Kevin and Meg to parts unknown.
所以你就能逃离我们的家族事业吗
So you just turned tail on the family business?
一家人都死光了还哪来的「家族」
Nothing says "family" quite like the whole family being dead.
我没有死
I wasn't dead.
事实上 我陷在上帝的腋窝里
In fact, I was knee-deep in God's armpit.
猎杀怪物
killing monsters,
我以为这是我们应该做的事
which, I thought, is what we actually do.
是的 迪恩
Yes, Dean.
就我所知 正是我们做的这些事
And far as I knew, what we do is the thing.
害死了我所有的家人
that got every single member of my family killed.
我一个亲人也没有了
I had no one … no one.
我有生以来 第一次完全孤立无助
And for the first time in my life, I was completely alone.
还有说实话 我没有地图
And, honestly, I didn't exactly have a roadmap.
所有我修好了英帕拉
So, yeah, I fixed up the Impala,
就开车上路
and I just…drove.
当然了 你先去找过我
After you looked for me.
你找我了吗 萨姆
Did you look for me, Sam?
好 很好
Good. That's good.
我们总是叮嘱对方
Now, we … we…always told each other.
不要去寻找对方
not to look for each other.
很明智 对你是好事
That's smart. Good for you.
当然 我们从来不管那个
Of course, we always ignored that.
因为我们对彼此有深厚不变的感情
because of our deep, abiding love for each another,
但这次你放弃了 是不是 萨姆
but not this time, right, Sammy?
迪恩 我还是原来那个我
Look, I'm still the same guy, Dean.
恭喜你
Well, bully for you.
我不是了
I'm not.
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
想吃点什么吗
You want some dinner?
不用了
Pass.
好吧
Okay.
怎么了
What?
萨姆·温彻斯特 我是凯文·谭
Sam Winchester, it's Kevin Tran.
克劳力把我关在一间仓库里
Crowley had me in this warehouse,
不过我逃出来了
and I just escaped.
我不知道我在哪儿
I don't know where I am.
我也不知道 他或者其他恶魔
And I don't know if he or … or any other demons.
是不是还在追杀我
are still after me.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
请回电 我是凯文·谭
Call me back. It's Kevin Tran.
什么时候打来的
When was that?
萨姆·温彻斯特 我是凯文·谭
Sam Winchester. It's Kevin Tran.
一周前我打来过
I called you a week ago.
请回电
Call me, please.
我不知道我该怎么办 兄弟
I don't know what the hell I'm doing out here, man.
哦
Okay.
我知道了
I get it.
那么 你想…
So, what, you want to…
- 制定计划什么的吗 - 萨姆 我是凯文
- strategize or something? - Sam, it's Kevin.
我很好
I'm good.
我非常好
Whoo! I'm so good.
他喝醉了
Is he…drunk?
自从三个月前你抛弃了我
3 months since you ditched my ass.
我就没睡过一个安稳觉
Haven't slept for more than four hours a night.
不过我还好啦
It's all good in the hood.
如果你还活着 去死吧
Uh, if you're still alive, eat me.
去死吧
Eat me.
萨姆 已经半年了
Sam, it's been 6 months.
我只能以为你已经死了
I can only assume you're dead.
如果你没死 也不要找我了
If not, don't try and reach me.
你找不到我的
You won't be able to.
我不会再打来了
I won't be calling this number anymore.
保护他是我们的责任
He was our responsibility.
你却连电话也不接
And you couldn't answer the damn phone.
好了 听这个
All right, listen to this …
凯文最后一条留言
Kevin's last message.
听听背景音
Listen to the background.
如果你没死 也不要找我了
If not, don't try and reach me.
你找不到我的
You won't be able to.
我不会再打来了
I won't be calling this number anymore.
听到了没
Hear that?
什么
What is it?
他好像在大巴上
I think he was on a bus.
再听一次
Listen again.
如果你没死 也不要找我了
If not, don't try and reach me.
终点站 山特维尔市
Last stop … Centreville.
不会再打来了
…won't be calling this number …
山特维尔市
Centreville?
- 山特维尔市在哪里 - 密歇根
- Centreville, where? - Michigan.
为什么凯文会在密歇根洲的山特维尔市
And why would Kevin be in Centreville, Michigan?
因为 他高中的女朋友
Because… his high-school girlfriend.
在那儿上大学
goes to college there.
（钱宁 山特维尔州立大学）
线索太少
That's thin.
这是最好的一条线索了
It's the best lead we got.
我们
"We"?
你说的对
You were right.
保护他是我们的责任
He was our responsibility.
那我们去找他 好吧
So…let's find him, okay?
貌似没伤害我的宝贝
Well… no visible signs of douchery …
这我承认
I'll give you that.
你闻到狗的味道了吗
Smell like dog to you?
车里吗
In the car?
你说呢
You tell me.
我打中你了
Come on. I got you.
不可能
No way.
你死定了
No, you are dead.
我才不会死呢
No way, I am not dead at all.
深呼吸
Take a breath.
冷静
Calm down.
天使在哪里
Where's the angel?
原来是你
You're him.
那个人类
The human.
天使在哪里
Where's the angel?
我不知道
I don't know.
你没事吧
You okay?
没事
Yeah.
我们离开这里 上路如何
Yeah, hey, what do you say we blow this joint, hit the road?
现在吗
Now?
对 凯文不会自己出现
Yeah, kevin's not getting any more found.
没我们 这孩子也活了一年
The kid survived a year without us.
再坚持12个小时应该没问题
He'll be okay for another 12 hours.
还有 你多久没睡觉了
Besides, when's the last time you slept?
什么
What?
没什么
Nothing.
你挂靴一年就是这么给自己找理由的吗
Is that, uh, that how you rationalized taking a year off?
没我们别人也不会有事
People will be okay?
是不会啊 迪恩
People were okay, Dean.
你也没事了
You're okay.
我履行了我们的承诺
Look, I did what we promised we'd do.
我放下过去 好好过日子
I moved on. I lived my life.
这我知道了
Yeah, no, I'm getting that.
我又不是什么都不管了
Look, it wasn't like I was…just oblivious.
我是说 我每天读报
I mean, I read the paper every day.
看到灵异事件
I saw the…weird stories,
我们以前对付的东西
the kind of stuff we used to chase.
然后你对自己说「不关我事」吗
And you said what? "Not my problem"?
对
Yes.
告诉你 地球还是一样转
And you know what? The world went on.
有人死去 萨姆
People died, Sam.
人总是要死的 迪恩
People will always die, Dean.
或许会有其他猎人去处理
Or maybe another hunter took care of it.
我不知道 我要说的是
I don't know, but the point is,
我第一次意识到
for the first time, I realized.
斩妖除魔不非得靠我一个
that it wasn't only up to me to stop it.
那是怎么回事
So what was it, hmm?
是什么让你就那么退出了
What could possibly make you stop just like that?
一个女孩
A girl?
是因为女孩吗
Was there a girl?
不关那女孩的事
The girl had nothing to do with it.
真有个女孩
There was a girl.
没错 是有过
Yeah. There was.
后来又没了
And then there wasn't.
还有什么问题
Any more questions?
我知道你会觉得难以置信
Listen, I know this is gonna sound crazy to you.
你不非得理解
I don't even necessarily need you to understand.
但你得知道
But…you need to know.
我不是突然就退出了 迪恩
I didn't just drop out, Dean.
我找到了一些东西
I found something.
一些我这辈子从未拥有的东西
Something I've…never had all my life.
她叫什么
What was her name?
艾米利亚
Amelia.
怎么
So, what, you, uh,
你们怎么搞在一起的
you dropped your peanut butter in her chocolate?
跟我讲讲
How'd it happen?
我撞了条狗
I hit a dog.
我就说有狗味儿
I knew I smelled dog.
我就知道你会发飙
And I knew you'd throw bitch fit.
这事很简单 萨姆
Hey, the rules are simple, Sam.
不抽陌生人的大麻
You don't take a joint from a guy named Don.
不带狗上车
And there's no dogs in the car!
好吧 你呢
All right, what about you?
- 我怎么了 - 你瞧瞧你
- What about me? - Look at you.
还是那副表情
You've still got that look.
紧张 不安
You're shaky. You're on edge.
那里什么样
What was it like?
我说了你也不会信
You wouldn't believe me if I told you.
试试看
Try me.
血腥
It was bloody.
肮脏
Messy.
各种底层的恶心东西
31 flavors of bottom-dwelling nasties.
大部分时候是上下左右受敌
Hell, most days felt like 360-degree combat.
但是在那里 有种感觉
But there was something about being there.
让我觉得纯粹
Felt pure.
怎么 救你一命都不说句谢谢
What? No thanks for saving you, ha?
好啊 我就不用这个捅死你了
Sure. I won't shove this up your ass?
就这么对待你生存下去的机会啊
Awful strange way to punch your meal ticket, friend.
我有你想要的东西
I got something you need.
什么东西
Yeah? What's that?
离开的方法
A way out.
就算你这种怪物也知道根本没法离开这儿
Even a dental apocalypse like you knows there's no such thing.
人就能离开
There is if you're human.
这是上帝的安排
God has made it so.
至少传言如此
At least, that's the rumor.
瞎扯
Bull.
随你吧
Suit yourself.
或许你是待惯了
Maybe you've gone native.
或许你就是喜欢留在这儿给人当饭吃
Maybe you like being man meat for every Tom, Dick, and Harry.
拿出证据
Prove it.
不行
Nah.
来不来拉倒
You're either in or you're out.
你就是善心大发
So you just want to guide me out of purgatory.
想带我离开炼狱吗
out of the goodness of your undead heart?
差不多吧
More or less.
你有什么好处
What's in it for you?
搭个顺风车
I'm hopping a ride.
什么
What?
那是个人类传送门 混蛋
It's a human portal, jackass.
仅限人类通过
Only humans can pass through.
我带你找到门
I show you the door,
你把我的灵魂带过去
you hump my soul to the other side.
那你是要辆灵魂列车（美国一档音乐节目）喽
So you're looking for a soul train.
是啊
Sure.
你喜欢这么说的话
If that's what you're into.
我怎么知道你不是给我下套
And how do I know this isn't a set-up?
我怎么知道我不会跟你朋友一个下场
How do I know I ain't gonna end up like your friend over there?
他曾是我朋友
He was my friend.
现在你是了
Now you are.
炼狱第一规则 孩子
First rule of purgatory, kid.
谁都别信
You can't trust nobody.
你刚刚还想让我信任你
You just asked me to trust you.
瞧
You see?
这不是开窍了
You're getting it now.
我们先去找天使
First we find the angel.
三个人太挤了
Mm, three's a crowd, chief.
没办法
Well, hey.
来不来拉倒
Either you're in or you're out.
我最后一次见凯文是一年前了
The last time I saw Kevin was, like, a year ago.
他失踪前吗
When he disappeared?
他偷了他妈妈的车
He stole his mother's car.
觉得自己要去完成什么上帝的任务
because he thought he was on a mission from God or something?
真是疯狂
It was crazy.
别那么说
Shut up!
我朋友亚当 嗑安非他命上瘾了
My friend Adam … who got addicted to adderall.
不过他SAT成绩超好 所以值了
but got a perfs on his S.A.T.s, so it was totally worth it.
- 也是这种情况 - 别说了
- same thing. - Shut up!
真的 也是上帝的任务
Seriously. Mission from God.
钱宁
Look, Channing,
我们知道凯文来过
we know Kevin was here.
他没来过
No, he wasn't.
如果你是想保护他 我们能理解
And we understand if you're trying to protect him.
但是我们才是最有能力保护他的人
But nobody can protect Kevin better than we can.
我讨厌他 才不会保护他呢
I hate Kevin. I wouldn't protect him.
你们不是一对儿吗
I thought you two had a thing.
他要去普林斯顿的时候我们是一对儿
Yeah, when he was going to Princeton.
这就情断义绝了
Wow. Just like that?
是啊
Yeah.
如果不是来见她 凯文跑来这儿干什么呢
So why would Kevin come sniffing around here if not to see her?
不知道
No idea.
或许我们该分头找
Maybe we should split up,
到处问问有没有人见过他
ask around, see if anybody's seen him?
是啊 在大学里找个这么高的亚裔人
Yeah, Asian kid, yea high, at a university.
肯定不是大海捞针了
That should be easy.
好了 你准备好忘记过去了吗
Okay. Are you ready to forget all about what's-his-name?
有个男生 叫凯尔 犹太人
Okay, this guy's name is Kyle, he's Jewish,
我可以确定他对亚裔女孩有好感
um, I'm pretty sure he has an Asian thing.
太棒了 是不是
Perfs, right?
闭嘴 贱人
Shut up, bitch.
[咒语]
先知还没来见我
The prophet still has not yet shown his face to me.
但是迪恩·温彻斯特回来了
But you should know Dean Winchester is back.
帮帮我 救救这只狗
Help. I need help. The dog needs help.
这边
That way!
他就那么突然冲出来
He just … he just came out of nowhere,
冲到我车前
right in front of my car.
得找个医生 你是医生吗
We need a doctor. Are you a doctor?
医生就来 先生 我不能确定
Doctor's coming sir, I'm not sure …
你不确定什么
You're not sure what.
这是动物医院 你们救治动物
This is an animal hospital. You save animals.
- 先生 - 快救救它
- Sir. - Save this animal!
罗伯塔 请你带这位先生出去
Roberta, can you escort this gentleman out, please?
好的
Yes.
是我撞了它
I did this.
走吧
Come on.
别瞧不起我
Don't judge me.
但我一无所获
I got bubkes.
那么…
Well…
- 给你 - 谢谢
- And here you go. - Ah, thank you.
真是太棒了
Sweet mother of God.
给我的 真的
It's for me? Seriously?
听听
Check this out.
我查了凯文应该在这儿
So, I went through campus security archives.
那段时间的校园保安档案
around the time Kevin should have been here.
觉得谁眼熟吗
Anyone look familiar?
伙计
Dude.
就是个汉堡
It's a burger.
是无价之宝
It's treasure.
那么凯文大老远跑来学校
All right, so, what, Kevin comes all the way to campus.
却不去见女友吗
and doesn't see his girlfriend?
不知道
I don't know…
但是我去了机房
But I went to the computer lab.
- 找到了他用过的电脑 - 然后呢
- and found the computer he was on. - And?
我查到了他浏览的网站
And I found the website he was visiting,
他的用户名 黑进了网站
found his account username, hacked in to the website,
查到这个用户名还在什么时候登陆过
found when else this username logged in,
然后反查IP地址
and then I reverse-tracked the I.P. address.
查到原始用户凯文
back to the original user, Kevin,
这两个月来 都在使用同一个
who is apparently been using the same wireless router.
无线路由器
for the past two months.
干得真棒
That is spectacular work.
能用人话再说一遍吗
Any chance I can get that in English?
嗯 我认为他在爱荷华
Yeah. I think he's in Iowa …
一间咖啡店里
At a coffee shop.
（爱荷华州 费尔菲尔德）
教堂 你确定没错吗
A church? You sure this is right?
咖啡店的吧员发誓说
Barista at the coffee shop swear.
他见到凯文过去几个月一直藏在这儿
he's seen Kenvin ducking in here for the past few months.
凯文
Kevin.
是萨姆和迪恩·温彻斯特 开门
It's Sam and Dean Winchester. Open up.
停下
Stop! Stop!
不是利维坦
Not Leviathans.
是我们
It's us.
你们去哪了
What the hell happened to you guys?
简单说
Cliff notes?
我去了炼狱 萨姆撞了狗
I went to purgatory. Sam hit a dog.
真的
For real?
要毛巾吗
You want some towels?
这都是谁教你的
Who taught you all this?
应该是上帝吧
I guess…God.
上帝教你怎么抓恶魔吗
God taught you how to trap demons?
严格来讲 是的
Technically, yeah.
等等
Wait, wait, hold on.
克劳利抓走了你 我看到了
Crowley kidnapped you. I saw that.
然后你留了条信息 说你逃出去了
But then you left a message saying you escaped.
怎么逃的
How?
这个嘛…
Well…
他先是带我去了一间仓库
First, he took me to a warehouse.
瞧瞧你
Look at you.
剪了个头发 手脚指甲都修了
Haircut, manicure, pedicure.
焕然一新啊
Like a new penny.
- 你们还要折磨我吗 - 折磨
- Will there be torture now? - Torture?
当然不了
Heavens, no.
不 恰恰相反 我的小王子
No. Quite the opposite, my young prince.
你我联合 不可阻挡
Sky's the limit for you and I.
那里有块碑
There was a tablet there,
就像之前那块
like the last one.
好了
There we go.
记住
Now, remember …
自信点 好好干
Feel like a winner, be a winner.
好吗
Okay?
翻译吧
Interpret.
还有一块碑
Wait, there's another tablet?
还有神之语
So another word of God.
对
Yes.
到底有多少神之语啊
How many words of God are there?
我一年前才成为先知的
I just became a prophet, like, a year ago.
这块碑有名字吗
Well, did this tablet have a name?
「恶魔」
"Demons."
恶魔怎么了
What about demons?
从我读到的来看
As far as I could tell…
差不多是关于恶魔的一切
everything.
这是什么东西
What are we looking at?
都是零零碎碎的
It's all just fragments.
东一句西一句
Bits and pieces.
这个有点难
This is hard.
给我点东西 凯文
Throw me a bone here, Kev.
等等
Wait…
怎么了
Yes?
抱歉 只有我觉得这里很热吗
I'm sorry. Is it just me, or is it hot in here?
是吗
Is it?
是我们的不对
Our mistake.
好了 我看到些东西
Okay. I see something.
地狱之门
Hell gates.
说说看
Talk to me.
地狱之门怎么了
What about hell gates?
威斯康星有扇门
There's one in Wisconsin.
碑上讲了怎么开启
The tablet told me how to open it.
还有一道咒语所需的材料
There were ingredients for a spell.
马上
Right away.
克劳利先生让你继续
Mr. Crowley would like you to proceed.
克劳利先生人呢
Where is Mr. Crowley?
你说呢 蠢货 当然在威斯康星
Where do you think, dumbass? Wisconsin.
动手啊
Go.
你告诉地狱之王怎么开启地狱之门了
You showed the king of hell how to open a hell gate?
让地狱里所有的恶魔一起跑出来
So that all the demons in hell could come out all at the same time?
什么
What?
当然不是
No.
人呢
Men?
凯文
Kevin?
我跟克劳利说我要开启地狱之门
I told Crowley I was opening a hell gate,
但我读的是另一个章节
but I was reading from another chapter …
如何杀死恶魔
how to destroy demons.
你个小坏蛋
You son of a bitch.
等等 凯文
Wait. Kevin?
那块碑呢
Where's the tablet now?
很安全
Safe.
在哪
Safe where?
安全就行了
Hey. As long as it's safe, okay?
你把碑藏起来之前还读到什么了吗
Were you able to read anything else off the tablet before you stash it?
只有怎么关上地狱之门
Only the stuff about closing the gate of Hell,
永远关闭
forever.
再说一遍
Come again?
驱逐地球上的所有恶魔
Banish all demons off the face of the earth.
把他们永远关起来
Lock them away forever.
应该挺重要的吧
That could be important, right?
永远关上地狱之门
Closing the gates of hell forever?
是啊 是该挺重要
Yeah. Yeah, that could be important.
这孩子如果说对了 他手里就有个重磅炸弹
Okay, if this kid is right, he's sitting on a bombshell.
他就是个那个重磅炸弹
Hell, he is the bombshell.
怎么了
What?
就这个
That.
凯文绝对不可能
I mean, there's no way that.
毫发无伤的完成这件事 对吧
Kevin's getting out of this intact, is there?
我觉得他到目前为止还挺能保护自己呢
Well, I think he's doing pretty well for himself so far.
那是因为他逃了
Yeah, he got out.
但现在他又加入了
And now he's in it…
不管他想不想
whether he likes it or not.
怎么 只有你能拥有自由意志吗
So…free will, that's only for you?
真不敢相信
I can't believe what I'm hearing.
萨姆 这可是消灭一切恶魔的机会
Sam, we have an opportunity to wipe the slate clean.
我们带凯文去找碑 他告诉我们咒语
We take Kevin to the tablet, he tells us the spell,
我们就能把所有恶魔永远关在地狱里
we send every demon back to hell … forever.
每一个毁了我们生活的混蛋
Every single basters that destroyed our lives,
那些杀了妈妈 杀了杰西的混蛋
killed our mother, killed Jess.
你还有什么疑虑
And you're not sure?
凯文
Kevin, I, uh…
我该向你道歉
I owe you an apology.
你和迪恩都消失掉的时候
Look, when you disappeared and Dean disappeared,
我得去清理下思路
I…needed to clear my head,
我想 有些事我本该去做 却没做
and…I'm thinking maybe you were one of the pieces.
救你就是其中之一
that I should have been there to pick up.
你从小就当上猎人了 是吗
You've been a hunter since you were a kid, right?
是啊 差不多
Yeah, mostly. Yeah.
自从我意识到我是一个先知
Ever since I realized I was a prophet…
很难相信这真的是我的生活
It's just hard to believe this is actually my life.
现在很糟糕 我知道
Yeah. It sucks right now. I know that.
可能还会再糟糕挺长一阵
Um, it might suck for a lot longer,
但是 相信我 一切会好起来的
But…trust me on this, it gets better.
你知道我不搞基吧
You know I'm not gay, right?
如果我们真能找回石碑
If we can do this, get the tablet,
给你一切关闭地狱之门所需的东西
get you everything you need to close the gates of hell,
我们就可以创造一个新的世界
There's a world out there where nobody …
再没有克劳力或者任何恶魔来追杀你
Not crowley, no demon … is chasing you anymore.
我想我只是不知道怎样走到那一步
I guess I just don't see how I get from here to there.
我以前也同样不知道
I used to not be able to see it, either.
但有方法的
But there is a way.
给我5分钟
Just give me 5 minutes.
它遭受了严重的内出血
He's sustained some serious internal bleeding.
目前我能看到至少有两条腿骨折
There's at least two leg fractures that I can see right now.
但是经过一些精心照料 它会渡过难关
But with some TLC, he should pull through for you.
谢谢你 医生
Thanks, doctor.
你会把狗带走吗
You're gonna take the dog?
我也想 但它不是我的
Look, I-I would. He's…not mine.
它就没有主人
He's not anybody's.
我经常在路上跑
I-I spend a lot of the time on the road.
你不觉得你有责任吗
Don't you think you're responsible?
我带它来就是觉得我负有责任
Why do you think I brought him here?
罗伯塔 他临走的时候请把他的奖杯给他
Roberta, could you hand this man his trophy on his way out, please?
如果你真那么正直
Well, maybe if you were such an upstanding guy,
或许就不会撞伤它了
you wouldn't have hit him in the first place?
好吧 我把它带走
Fine. I'll take him.
这才是英雄
There's my hero.
有人来了
We got company.
萨姆
Sam.
那是什么
What the hell is that?
炼狱神器
It's purgatory.
迪恩·温彻斯特 从炼狱回来了
Dean winchester. Back from purgatory.
恶魔史班奇 我听说过你
Spanky the demon. Yeah, I heard about you.
老爱咬人的那个 对吧
The one who uses too much teeth, right?
迪恩
Dean!
你们好啊 孩子们
Hello, boys.
迪恩
Dean.
你看起来
You're looking…
只能说炼狱对你没什么好处
Well, let's just say purgatory didn't do you any favors.
你的天使呢
Where's your angel?
问你妈去
Ask your mother.
你又来那小孩脾气
There's that grade-school zip.
我真的好怀念
Missed it. I really did.
小鹿
Moose.
还那么膀呢
Still with the pork chops.
让我钦佩
I admire that.
放钱宁走
Let Channing go.
凯文 那不是钱宁
That's not Channing, kevin.
现在不是了
Not anymore.
你怎么能说这种话
What an awful thing to say to the boy.
这当然还是钱宁
Of course it's Channing.
凯文
Kev.
我们上次合作时
Last time we danced,
你偷了我的石碑还杀了我的人
You stole my tablet and killed my men.
这样吧
Tell you what.
现在跟我走 那些事一笔勾销
Come with me now, bygones.
然后我会让这女孩回到从前的样子
And I'll let the girl go back to…what's-the-point u.
他在骗人
He's lying.
钱宁不会变回来 她可能已经死了
You won't get Channing back. She's probably dead already.
你能别这样说吗
Will you please stop saying that?
让那女孩说话
Let the girl speak.
- 凯文 - 钱宁
- Kevin? - Channing?
发生什么了
What's going on?
有一个恶魔在你体内
There's a demon in you,
你去你的保底学校念书了
And you're going to your safety school.
- 什么 - 但你会没事的
- What?! - But it's gonna be okay.
真受不了
I-I-I-I just … I can't.
不要 等等
No, no, wait.
好吧
Okay.
我跟你走
I'll do it.
- 凯文 - 用我换那个女孩
- Kevin. - Myself for the girl.
但这事就此为止
But this ends.
好吗 别再打了
All right? No fighting, no nothing.
这事结束了
It ends.
不能让你这么做 伙计
Can't let you do that, buddy.
不然呢
Or what?
你杀了我
You'll kill me?
我去收拾东西
I'll grab my stuff.
各位振作起来
Chin up, gentlemen.
我可是专家
I'm a professional.
这事没完 克劳力
This ain't over by a long shot, Crowley.
你这台词都谁写的 毫无气力
Really, Dean, who writes your stuff? A marshmallow?
走了 凯文
Come on, Kevin.
快点
Chop-chop.
凯文
Kevin?
太天真了吧 孩子们
Really, boys?
凯文
Kevin!
Kevin.
萨姆 迪恩 快跑
Sam, Dean, run!
再去找个肉身来
Find another meatsuit.
你好
Hello.
打错了
Wrong number.
一蠢货打来的电话
Call that made by a jackass.
有人想要什么吗
Alright, anybody want anything?
我不要
I'm good.
凯文
Kevin?
你还好吗
How're you holding up?
棒极了
Awesome.
地狱之王刚扭断了我女朋友的脖子
The king of hell just snapped my girlfriend's neck.
你觉得呢
How about you?
好吧 听我说
All right, listen to me.
我对你女朋友的事很遗憾 真的
I'm sorry about your girlfriend, okay? I am.
你越早想通对你越好
But the sooner you get this, the better.
无论你喜不喜欢 你已经牵扯进来了
You're in it now whether you like it or not.
这意味着你要做你必须做的事
That means you do what you got to do.
我去上个厕所
I'm hitting the head.
你打来了
There he is.
你怎么弄到手机的
How did you get a phone?
你能相信这东西现在便利店就有卖的吗
Would you believe they sell these things in convenience stores now?
50年变化很大啊
A lot's changed in 50 years.
一定有很多东西要适应
Must be a hell of a lot to take in.
最大的变化是选择 你懂吗
Mostly it's the choices, you know?
好多选择
So many choices.
我听到了
Yeah, I hear that.
本尼 我不想多费唇舌
Listen, benny, not to beat a dead horse.
但是我们在下面做了必须做的
What we did down there is what we had to do.
即使是现在 我也一点不后悔
Now, I don't regret it for a second.
但是 或许在我们适应地上生活之前
But…you know, maybe until we both adjust,
最好先不要联系了
It's best we don't talk for a while.
又来了
There it is.
一天一次 就像我们之前说的那样
One day at a time, just like we talked about, right?
我觉得你是对的 兄弟
I think you had it right, bud.
什么
What's that?
炼狱是很纯粹
Purgatory was pure.
真希望我当时知道珍惜
I'm kinda wish that I had appreciated it more.
知道吗
You know?
就像你那样
Like you.
你要是有紧急情况就打电话给我 知道吗
Listen, you got an emergency, you call me, you understand?
我听到了
I hear you.
你也别惹事 兄弟
You keep your nose clean, too, brother.
好的
Yeah.